💞 kissasian.one 💞
💞 kissasian.one 💞
Didn't you say you would give me a reward?
Non hai detto che mi avresti dato una ricompensa?
Why do I feel like you are using me as a backrest?
Mi stai usando come schienale.
You want a reward?
Vuoi un premio?
Of course.
Certo.
You dragged me into doing so many things and I agreed to all of them.
Mi hai trascinato a fare un sacco di cose e non mi sono tirato indietro.
Well, turn around.
Allora… girati.
Why?
Perché?
Obedient kids get candy.
I bambini obbedienti ottengono caramelle.
Why would someone willingly stay by your side?
Perché qualcuno dovrebbe rimanere al tuo fianco?
Why would one person be so kind to another?
Perché qualcuno dovrebbe essere così gentile con qualcun altro?
[Newton and the Apple]
[Newton e la mela]
♫ When I think of you ♫
♫ Quando penso a te ♫
♫ I think about the first time we met ♫
♫ Mi viene in mente la prima volta che ti ho visto ♫
♫ Suddenly my heart flipped ♫
♫ All'improvviso il mio cuore ha sussultato ♫
♫ And I fall into the life of a drama play ♫
♫ E sono finito nella vita di un drama ♫
♫ You're Newton and I'm the apple ♫
♫ Tu sei Newton e io la mela ♫
♫ Falling from the tree ♫
♫ Che cade dall'albero ♫
♫ Oh, take a bite ♫
♫ Oh, dai un morso ♫
♫ Just like fish needs water ♫
♫ Proprio come i pesci hanno bisogno dell'acqua ♫
♫ You're summer and I'm the breeze ♫
♫ Tu sei l'estate e io la brezza ♫
♫ I don't understand why love always makes people feel at a loss ♫
♫ Non capisco perché l'amore ci fa sempre sentire in difficoltà ♫
💞 kissasian.one 💞
💕 Stay by My Side 👻
[Episode 5] Gu Buxia.
Episodio 5 👻 Gu Buxia.
Stop acting dumb.
Smetti di fare il finto tonto.
Help me find my daughter.
Aiutami a trovare mia figlia.
What should we do? He seems to really not hear us.
Che facciamo? Sembra non sentirci.
Could it be his power has been temporarily sealed by Yang energy?
Potrebbe essere per via del potere sigillato dall'energia dello Yang?
It seems like every time that guy Jiang Chi is around,
Sembra che ogni volta che c'è quel Jiang Chi nei dintorni
Gu Buxia can't hear us.
Gu Buxia non riesca a sentirci.
Recently, I've been staying close to my roommate
Di recente, sono stato molto col mio coinquilino
and haven't heard those ghost voices for a while.
e non ho più sentito quelle voci.
Bring him back here someday.
Portalo qui un giorno di questi.
I'll take a look for you.
Gli darò un'occhiata.
It's not like a boyfriend meets the family.
Non è mica un incontro fidanzato-famiglia.
Besides, I can't always depend on him.
E poi, non posso sempre dipendere da lui.
What if he ignores me one day?
E se un giorno mi ignorasse?
I still have to be independent and strong.
Devo essere indipendente e forte lo stesso.
Pluck the flower when it blooms,
Cogli il fiore quando sboccia,
or you'll be left with the branches.
o resterai con i rami.
You'll just have to save up more normally.
Dovrai solo risparmiare di più.
What's wrong?
Che c'è?
My dad fainted while he was seeing a patient.
Mio padre è svenuto mentre visitava un paziente.
I need to go back and check on him.
Devo tornare a casa.
Is he okay now?
Sta bene adesso?
I don't know.
Non lo so.
I don't know when I can come back.
Non so quando tornerò.
Can you manage alone?
Ce la farai da solo?
Of course. Hurry and go see your dad. Take care.
Certo. Corri da tuo padre. Fai attenzione.
Call me if you need anything.
Chiamami se ti serve qualcosa.
Don't forget to call me.
Non scordarti di telefonarmi.
Jiang Chi has left. This is our chance.
Jiang Chi se n'è andato. È la nostra occasione.
No way.
Assurdo.
Someone's father is sick.
Il padre di qualcuno sta male.
Even as ghosts, we should have a conscience.
Anche se siamo fantasmi, dovremmo avere una coscienza.
Don't say we ghosts don't have a conscience.
Non dire che non ce l'abbiamo.
I'm so cold that feel like I could die again.
Ho talmente freddo che mi sembra di morire di nuovo.
I can't be bothered about conscience anymore.
Chi se ne importa della coscienza.
Gu Buxia, can you hear us? Student Gu.
Gu Buxia, ci senti? Studente Gu.
He heard us.
Ci sente!
No way.
Non è possibile.
It's only the second day without being with Jiang Chi.
È solo il secondo giorno senza Jiang Chi.
And my quota dropped so fast.
Ed è crollato tutto.
There should still be some of Jiang Chi's Yang energy here.
Qui ci dev'essere un po' di energia di Jiang Chi.
Gu Buxia, don't be afraid.
Gu Buxia, non aver paura.
You have to be strong.
Devi essere forte.
Jiang Chi will be back soon.
Jiang Chi tornerà presto.
No. We have to be brave and depend on ourselves.
No. Devo essere coraggioso e indipendente.
You'll get used to it if you listen for a while.
Ti ci abituerai se ascolti per un po'.
It's useless.
È inutile.
Just do as we say.
Fai come diciamo.
Child.
Ragazzo.
Don't be afraid.
Non avere paura.
Just help us out.
Aiutaci e basta.
Stop harassing me.
Lasciatemi in pace!
My Jiang Chi will be back soon.
Il mio Jiang Chi tornerà presto.
[Yong Yu Gymnasium]
[Palestra Yong Yu]
Move!
Muoviti!
- Are you okay? - Hey.
- Stai bene? - Ehi.
I'm fine.
Sto bene.
Let's help him up first.
Aiutiamolo.
Are you in any pain?
Senti dolore?
No way.
Non è possibile.
Did you break up with Jiang Chi?
Hai rotto  Jiang Chi?
Gu Buxia, have you lost your soul?
Gu Buxia, hai perso la tua anima?
Where's Jiang Chi? I haven't seen him these days.
Dov'è Jiang Chi? Non lo vedo da giorni.
He's got some family matters,
Ha questioni di famiglia,
so he'll be gone for a few days.
starà via per qualche giorno.
It's only a few days.
Sono solo pochi giorni.
But why does he look like he's been dumped?
Perché sembra che sia stato scaricato?
You don't understand.
Non capisci.
This is what people call "A day apart feels like three seasons."
Questo è il cosiddetto "pochi giorni che sembrano un'eternità".
Let's go.
Andiamo.
You'll be okay. Right?
Starai bene.
Once upon a time, I was good at basketball.
Una volta ero bravo a basket.
But it seems their basketball team isn't doing well these past two years.
Però, sono due anni che la loro squadra non va bene.
Gu Buxia, why do you look so weak?
Gu Buxia, perché sembri così debole?
Dear uncles, aunts, brothers, and sisters, please spare me.
Cari zii, zie, fratelli e sorelle. Per favore, risparmiatemi.
Let me get some good sleep tonight.
Fatemi dormire un po' stanotte.
Don't always be so fierce.
Non essere sempre così aggressivo.
Or else, if this continues,
Altrimenti, se continuate,
I will be headed to your place.
mi ritroverò dalla vostra parte.
Child,
Ragazzo,
don't be afraid.
non temere.
We came first, and you haven't solved our issues.
Siamo arrivati primi e non ci hai aiutati con i nostri problemi.
When others hear about this and come,
Quando altri lo sapranno,
you will surely go crazy.
impazzirai di sicuro.
How's your dad?
Come sta tuo padre?
He's stable now.
È stabile.
But no caretaker can stand him.
Ma nessun infermiere lo sopporta.
So I have to take care of him.
Quindi devo occuparmi io di lui.
What about your mom, your brother, and your sister?
E tua madre, tuo fratello e tua sorella?
Can't you take turns?
Non potete fare a turni?
Won't it be exhausting like this?
Non sarà estenuante così?
Doctors don't have time to take care of their family. I'm all right.
I dottori non hanno tempo da dedicare alla famiglia. Io sto bene.
Do you need anything? I can bring it for you.
Ti serve qualcosa? Te lo posso portare.
Nope, it's all very convenient here.
No, qui c'è tutto.
What about school?
E la scuola?
If you need anything, you have to tell me.
Se ti serve qualcosa, me lo devi dire.
Worry about yourself instead.
Preoccupati per te.
Without a translator by your side, you need to work harder.
Senza un traduttore al tuo fianco, devi lavorare di più.
Gu Buxia, come closer.
Gu Buxia, avvicinati.
Why do you have heavy dark circles?
Perché hai le occhiaie?
Are you not sleeping well without me?
Non dormi bene senza di me?
I didn't sleep well because of the game.
Non dormo bene per via del gioco.
How could it be because of you?
Come potrebbe essere per te?
All right, I will go to bed earlier.
Va bene, ora vado a letto.
Remember not to look too serious.
Ricorda di non sembrare troppo serio.
Don't be mean to the patient.
Non essere cattivo con tuo padre.
Remember to thank the nurse.
Ricorda di ringraziare le infermiere.
I'm in the middle of a game.
Sono nel bel mezzo del gioco.
I have to go now.
Devo andare.
[Wait for me to come back.]
[Aspetta il mio ritorno]
If Jiang is not here, Gu can't block us.
Se non c'è Jiang, Gu non può fermarci.
- When he's back, I'll see what you have to say. - Just ignore him.
- Quando tornerà, vedremo cosa avrete da dire. - Ignoriamolo.
I hope Jiang moves out soon.
Spero che Jiang si trasferisca presto.
You relied on Jiang Chi, but he's gone now.
Hai fatto affidamento su Jiang Chi, ma ora se n'è andato.
It's best to rely on oneself.
Meglio fare affidamento su se stessi.
I'm not around, will he be okay by himself?
Non ci sono, starà bene?
Running anywhere is useless.
Scappare è inutile.
Let's see who can last longer.
Vediamo chi resiste di più.
But he doesn't have the incense smell.
Ma non ha l'odore dell'incenso.
Perhaps it's useless to talk to him?
Forse è inutile parlare con lui?
Even if it's useless, we must continue.
Anche se è inutile, dobbiamo continuare.
We finally caught someone
Finalmente abbiamo beccato qualcuno
who can hear our voices.
che può sentire le nostre voci.
While that person hasn't returned,
Visto che quella persona non è ancora tornata,
shall we wake him up first?
lo svegliamo?
Otherwise, once he touches him…
Altrimenti, appena lo tocca…
He won't be able to hear us.
Non ci sentirà più.
That man is back.
È tornato.
Every time he gets close to this kid,
Ogni volta che si avvicina al ragazzo,
it seems like there's a shield.
sembra che gli faccia da scudo.
♫ Wanting what you can't ask for is a luxury ♫
♫ Volere qualcosa che non puoi chiedere è un lusso ♫
♫ Wanting what you can easily get is a habit ♫
♫ Volere qualcosa che puoi avere facilmente è un'abitudine ♫
♫ The time that is quiet, anesthetizes you and me ♫
♫ Il tempo silenzioso ci anestetizza ♫
♫ Our love is still there ♫
♫ Il nostro amore è ancora lì ♫
♫ Close your eyes, brush your teeth and wash your face ♫
♫ Chiudi gli occhi, lavati i denti e il viso ♫
You're finally back.
Finalmente sei tornato.
♫ Because I know you too well, my dear ♫
♫ Perché ti conosco troppo bene, mio caro ♫
♫ What you didn't say, let me tell you first ♫
♫ Quello che non hai detto, te lo dico io ♫
You must be tired, Jiang.
Devi essere stanco, Jiang.
Welcome back.
Bentornato.
Let me, as your roommate, make up for it.
Lasciami rimediare.
What do you want?
Che cosa vuoi?
♫ Sorry to make you feel like something's missing ♫
♫ Mi dispiace se sentivi che mancava qualcosa ♫
♫ I gave you all I could give ♫
♫ Ti ho dato tutto quello che ho potuto ♫
♫ But it was barely a passing score ♫
♫ Ma era a malapena la sufficienza ♫
♫ If I'm just someone you need ♫
♫ Se hai solo bisogno di me ♫
Thank you for making up for it.
Grazie per aver rimediato.
♫ Quitting this habit would be worth it ♫
♫ Smettere questa abitudine ne varrebbe la pena ♫
♫ I wish you could be happier than now ♫
♫ Vorrei che fossi più felice di adesso ♫
Next time getting a kiss, remember to close your eyes.
La prossima volta, ricordati di chiudere gli occhi.
You…
Tu…
Why did you kiss me?
Perché mi hai baciato?
You seemed to want that.
Sembrava che lo volessi.
No, I didn't.
No, invece.
You didn't?
Non volevi?
Did I?
Sembrava così?
I didn't, right?
No, giusto?
Okay, you didn't. It was me.
Va bene, non volevi. Ero io a volerlo.
I was too tired these days, and seeing you made me happy.
Ero troppo stanco in questi giorni e vederti mi ha reso felice.
We're both men. You won't mind. Right?
Siamo uomini, ma non importa. Giusto?
We're both men.
Siamo uomini.
It's okay. Right?
Va bene, no?
I don't mind.
Non fa nulla.
We two with panda eyes should be able to sleep well tonight, right?
Sembriamo due panda con queste borse, andiamo a dormire.
[A. No loud talking, B. Table and Chairs should be put back in place after use, C. Keep the environment clean and tidy. THANKS!!]
[A. Non si parla a voce alta. | B. Tavoli e sedie vanno rimessi a posto. | C. Tenere pulito e ordinato. Grazie!!]
♫ Go, going left, going right, and where to ♫
♫ Vai a sinistra, vai a destra ♫
♫ This is the junction most familiar to me every day ♫
♫ È l'incrocio a me più famigliare ♫
♫ The rhythm was disrupted by you ♫
♫ Hai interrotto il mio ritmo ♫
♫ The sky is sometimes clear, sometimes cloudy, and sometimes rainy ♫
♫ Il cielo a volte è limpido, altre è nuvoloso e piove ♫
♫ Slippery weather forecast, slippery IG, slipping and sliding, I lose myself ♫
♫ Il vento e il mare vanno e vengono e io mi sono perso ♫
♫ I want to block my thoughts of you ♫
♫ Voglio bloccare i miei pensieri ♫
♫ My vision has run wild and my hearing is wrong, and I even laugh unconsciously ♫
♫ La mia vista si scatena e il mio udito si sbaglia e rido senza rendermene conto ♫
If this goes on, I won't be able to leave him anymore.
Se continua così, non riuscirò più a lasciarlo.
What should I do?
Cosa dovrei fare?
Here, this is for you.
Ecco, per te.
I'm going to shower.
Vado a farmi una doccia.
Wait for me for a bit.
Aspettami.
Why should I wait for you?
Perché dovrei?
Why would I care if you shower or not?
Perché dovrebbe interessarmi se ti fai la doccia o no?
Bad habit.
Pessima abitudine.
[Yong Yu Gymnasium]
[Palestra Yong Yu]
- Good morning. - Morning.
- Buongiorno. - 'Giorno.
- Your defense needs to be solid. - Baiwei, you're up.
- La difesa dev'essere solida. - Baiwei, vai tu.
Okay.
Sì.
- Keep your hands low. - Yes.
- Tieni basse le mani. - Sì.
- Gu Buxia. - Morning.
- Gu Buxia. - 'Giorno.
You're late. Where is Jiang Chi?
Sei in ritardo. Dov'è Jiang Chi?
Captain, there he is.
Capitano, eccolo.
♫ When I'm lonely, I will vigorously count the unhurried fingertips ♫
♫ Quando sarò solo, conterò sulle dita senza fretta ♫
♫ I'm stupid crazy, thinking of you buying my smile with a piece of candy ♫
♫ Sono un pazzo a pensare che compri il mio sorriso con una caramella ♫
- Welcome, welcome. - Thank you for joining us.
- Benvenuto. - Grazie per esserti unito alla squadra.
If you want to thank someone, thank Gu Buxia.
È Gu Buxia che dovete ringraziare.
He needs me.
Ha bisogno di me.
Don't forget the conditions we agreed on.
Non dimenticatevi le condizioni che abbiamo stabilito.
The only practice combination that cannot be separated.
La combinazione pratica che non può essere separata.
Brand new designated number 11 jersey.
Una nuova divisa numero 11.
And a jersey towel, designated for Gu Buxia to wash personally.
Asciugamano destinato a Gu Buxia.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming today?
Perché non mi hai detto che saresti venuto?
To thank you for the supplements you gave me.
Per ringraziarti degli integratori che mi hai dato.
Supplements?
Integratori?
Hey, what are you two whispering about?
Ehi, cosa bisbigliate?
We're all brothers here.
Siamo tutti compagni di squadra.
Buxia asked why I joined the basketball team.
Buxia mi ha chiesto perché mi sono unito alla squadra.
Why?
Perché?
Because I ate the supplements from Gu Buxia.
Perché ho preso gli integratori di Gu Buxia.
Last night…
Ieri sera…
Last night, he was convinced by my heartfelt persuasion.
Ieri sera, è stato convinto dalla mia sincera persuasione.
You should all give your thanks to me.
Dovreste tutti ringraziare me.
- Impressive. - Of course.
- Notevole. - Ovvio.
- Let's start practicing. - Okay.
- Cominciamo. - Sì.
Pass the ball.
Passami la palla.
What supplements?
Quali integratori?
Give me the ball. Here.
Passatemi la palla.
Why are you buying groceries and cooking for no reason?
Perché hai fatto la spesa e cucinato senza motivo?
Didn't you say you wanted to make it up for me?
Non avevi detto che volevi rimediare?
Please. We can order delivery or eat out.
Possiamo ordinare da mangiare o uscire.
That's not sincere enough.
Non sei abbastanza sincero.
I really can't cook.
Non so proprio cucinare.
No. I've never even cooked instant noodles before.
Peggio. Non so nemmeno cucinare i noodle istantanei.
You were so good to me before,
Sei stato buono con me prima,
and now that you have me, you're planning to slack off?
e ora che sono tuo, batti la fiacca?
What do you mean "have you"?
Come sarebbe "sei mio"?
I can do other things that I'm good at for you.
Posso fare altre cose in cui sono bravo.
Things you're good at?
In cui sei bravo?
Gu Buxia.
Gu Buxia.
What are you daydreaming about?
A cosa stavi pensando?
I was thinking about pandas.
Pensavo ai panda.
Your dark circles are still quite obvious.
Le tue occhiaie sono evidenti.
You're not much better.
Tu non sei messo meglio.
Should we sleep together again tonight?
Stanotte dormiamo insieme di nuovo?
I'll leave the rest to you.
Lascio fare a te.
Oh, okay.
Va bene.
Why are your ears so red?
Perché hai le orecchie rosse?
It's all your fault.
È colpa tua.
Why did you get so close for no reason?
Ti avvicini senza motivo.
Don't you also get close to those guys from the basketball team?
Non stai vicino anche agli altri della squadra?
I'm not used to it.
Non sono abituato.
They're not like you.
Loro non sono come te.
What am I like?
Come sono io?
Are you on strike?
Sei in sciopero?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Vado in bagno.
Jiang Chi, have you seen this before?
Jiang Chi, l'hai mai vista questa?
You haven't seen it?
Tu no?
Everyone's been passing it around lately.
Se la girano tutti ultimamente.
Deadlock. [Jiang Chi &amp; Buxia]
Vicolo cieco. [Jiang Chi + Buxia]
It's all your fault.
È tutta colpa tua.
Your actions caused misunderstandings.
Le tue azioni creano malintesi.
Should we explain?
Dovremmo dare una spiegazione?
Explain what?
Spiegazione per cosa?
Or do you not want to make it public?
O vuoi dirlo a tutti?
Can anyone tell me
Qualcuno può dirmi
what we are going to make public?
che cosa dovremmo dire a tutti?
💞 kissasian.one 💞
💞 kissasian.one 💞
♫ Don't leave me stranded in a sea of people ♫
♫ Non lasciarmi bloccato tra la folla ♫
♫ Crying for help on an island of memories ♫
♫ Mentre chiedo aiuto su un'isola di ricordi ♫
♫ I don't want anyone to find out ♫
♫ Non voglio che qualcuno lo scopra ♫
♫ But just want you to hear me ♫
♫ Voglio solo che mi ascolti ♫
♫ I miss you ♫
♫ Mi manchi ♫
♫ Like a wildfire ♫
♫ Come un incendio ♫
♫ Breaking taboos and boundaries ♫
♫ Distruggi i tabù e i confini ♫
♫ Spreading endlessly ♫
♫ Ti espandi senza fine ♫
♫ Did you hear that? ♫
♫ L'hai sentito? ♫
♫ I finally understand ♫
♫ Finalmente capisco ♫
♫ The words I never said to you ♫
♫ Le parole che non ti ho detto ♫
♫ Please answer me if you can hear me ♫
♫ Per favore, se mi senti, rispondimi ♫
♫ Okay? ♫
♫ Va bene? ♫
💞 kissasian.one 💞
💕 Stay by My Side 👻
[Preview]
Anteprima 👻
When one person kisses another,
Quando una persona ne bacia un'altra,
what is the real reason hidden behind lofty pretenses?
qual è il vero motivo nascosto?
What's wrong with me?
Cos'ho che non va?
Is this a move between brothers?
È una cosa che succede tra amici?
He kissed me, but why didn't I dodge?
Mi ha baciato, ma perché non l'ho fermato?
It's not a misunderstanding. I meant what I said.
Non è un malinteso. Intendevo davvero ciò che ho detto.